{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question_number": 1,
      "question": "Pick the awesome one",
      "question_name": "Pick One",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "no hint baby",
      "answer": "4",
      "explanation": "For obvious reasons",
      "message": "Hello, from the other side",
      "pad_characters": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "choice": "Dhruv"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Rohan"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Rishabh"
        },
        {
          "choice": "All of the above"
        }
      ],
      "layout_type": 0
    },
    {
      "question_number": 2,
      "question": "Aviral is a __ boy",
      "question_name": "Aviral",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "Think more on this",
      "answer": "GOOD",
      "explanation": "well maybe I am lying here",
      "message": "Its too late to apologize",
      "pad_characters": "GOODEBADWREQ",
      "options": [],
      "layout_type": 1
    },
    {
      "question_number": 3,
      "question": "Gauri is a __ boy",
      "question_name": "Gauri",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "Think more on this",
      "answer": "3",
      "explanation": "no",
      "message": "Its too late to apologize",
      "pad_characters": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "choice": "happy"
        },
        {
          "choice": "good"
        },
        {
          "choice": "smart"
        },
        {
          "choice": "sad"
        }
      ],
      "layout_type": 0
    },
    {
      "question_number": 4,
      "question": "Dhruv is a __ boy",
      "question_name": "Dhruv",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "Think more on this",
      "answer": "HARAMI",
      "explanation": "no",
      "message": "Its too late to apologize",
      "pad_characters": "HARAMIHQWPLX",
      "options": [],
      "layout_type": 2
    },
    {
      "question_number": 5,
      "question": "Dhaval is a ___ bwoy.",
      "question_name": "Dhaval",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "Think more on this",
      "answer": "STUDIOUS",
      "explanation": "well maybe I am lying here",
      "message": "Its too late to apologize",
      "pad_characters": "LASWSTUDIOUS",
      "options": [],
      "layout_type": 1
    },
    {
      "question_number": 6,
      "question": "Saare ke saare ga ma ko ke lar ___ chale",
      "question_name": "Saare Ke Saare",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "Think more on this",
      "answer": "GAATE",
      "explanation": "no",
      "message": "Its too late to apologize",
      "pad_characters": "WGAATEPLKASH",
      "options": [],
      "layout_type": 2
    },
    {
      "question_number": 7,
      "question": "My Android Studio Version is?",
      "question_name": "Pick One",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "no hint baby",
      "answer": "4",
      "explanation": "For obvious reasons",
      "message": "Hello, from the other side",
      "pad_characters": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "choice": "1.4"
        },
        {
          "choice": "1.5"
        },
        {
          "choice": "1.7"
        },
        {
          "choice": "2.0"
        }
      ],
      "layout_type": 0
    },
    {
      "question_number": 8,
      "question": "Nivea is ",
      "question_name": "Dhruv",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "Think more on this",
      "answer": "LOTION",
      "explanation": "no",
      "message": "Its too late to apologize",
      "pad_characters": "LPWRDFLOTION",
      "options": [],
      "layout_type": 2
    },
    {
      "question_number": 9,
      "question": "Oh sugar, you dont have to be so sweet",
      "question_name": "Aviral",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "Think more on this",
      "answer": "GOOD",
      "explanation": "well maybe I am lying here",
      "message": "Its too late to apologize",
      "pad_characters": "DAFGEBADGOOD",
      "options": [],
      "layout_type": 1
    },
    {
      "question_number": 10,
      "question": "Dhruv is a __ boy",
      "question_name": "Dhruv",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "Think more on this",
      "answer": "HARAMI",
      "explanation": "no",
      "message": "Its too late to apologize",
      "pad_characters": "HARAMIHQWPLX",
      "options": [],
      "layout_type": 2
    },
    {
      "question_number": 11,
      "question": "Dhruv is a __ boy",
      "question_name": "Dhruv",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "Think more on this",
      "answer": "HARAMI",
      "explanation": "no",
      "message": "Its too late to apologize",
      "pad_characters": "HARAMIHQWPLX",
      "options": [],
      "layout_type": 2
    },
    {
      "question_number": 12,
      "question": "Dhruv is a __ boy",
      "question_name": "Dhruv",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "Think more on this",
      "answer": "HARAMI",
      "explanation": "no",
      "message": "Its too late to apologize",
      "pad_characters": "HARAMIHQWPLX",
      "options": [],
      "layout_type": 2
    },
    {
      "question_number": 13,
      "question": "Pick the awesome one",
      "question_name": "Pick One",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "no hint baby",
      "answer": "4",
      "explanation": "For obvious reasons",
      "message": "Hello, from the other side",
      "pad_characters": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "choice": "Dhruv"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Rohan"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Rishabh"
        },
        {
          "choice": "All of the above"
        }
      ],
      "layout_type": 0
    },
    {
      "question_number": 14,
      "question": "Pick the awesome one",
      "question_name": "Pick One",
      "category": 1,
      "hint": "no hint baby",
      "answer": "4",
      "explanation": "For obvious reasons",
      "message": "Hello, from the other side",
      "pad_characters": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "choice": "Dhruv"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Rohan"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Rishabh"
        },
        {
          "choice": "All of the above"
        }
      ],
      "layout_type": 0
    }
  ]
}